whoscored.com 2014-12-23

# Terms of Use

We use cookies to give you the best experience on our website. By using our site, you agree to our use of cookies. Learn more OK

WhoScored.com aims to deliver content as accurate and fast as possible, however we are not responsible for inaccurate and delayed content.

Visitors are not allowed to copy, download, reproduce, republish, frame, broadcast, transmit in any manner whatsoever, unless there is express written consent given by WhoScored.com and there is a clear link back to "WhoScored.com." Any activity against this Article will be viewed as a direct violation of our policy.

 **What information do we collect?**

WhoScored.com collects information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter. When registering on WhoScored.com, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. **What does WhoScored.com use your information for?**  Any of the information WhoScored.com collects from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience  
To improve our website  
To improve customer service  
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
To send periodic emails

**How does WhoScored.com protect your information?**  WhoScored.com implements a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.  **Cookies**  

Cookies are small text files that a site can place on your computer or mobile device to store certain information. We use cookies to keep track of how you use our website, remember if you are logged in or not, make our website work efficiently, and deliver relevant content including advertisement.

You can set up your browser not to allow cookies, however some parts our site would not function properly. You can get more information about cookies here: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

 **Third party links**  

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. 

WhoScored.com have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. **Your Consent**  

By using 

WhoScored.com, you consent to our websites privacy policy. **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on June 27, 2014.
